ELIZABETH ARYSLANOVA

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

C

+995 591 923 164

 \checkmark

e.aryslanova@gmail.com

in

/elizabeth-aryslanova



LizAryslanova.github.io



github.com/LizAryslanova



Batumi, Georgia

SUMMARY

Self-taught machine learning engineer with a master's degree in optics and a background in mathematical modeling. With 15 years of dedicated mathematics teaching experience and a successful track record in online course production and consulting on 20+ projects.

EDUCATION

POSTGRADUATE DEGREE (Unfinished)

Mathematical Modeling, Numerical Methods and Software Solutions ITMO University 2014 - 2018

MASTER OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Photonics and Optical Information Technology ITMO University 2012 - 2014

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Photonics and Optical Information Technology ITMO University 2008 - 2012

SKILLS

Programming & Frameworks

Python, PyTorch, Librosa, NumPy, SciPy, Matplotlib, HTML, CSS

Software

Final Cut, DaVinci Resolve, Logic Pro X, Affinity Photo, Affinity Designer, Wolfram Mathematica

Other

Capturing visuals, Public speaking, Teaching, Simplifying complexity, Soldering, Audio recording

LANGUAGES

English, Russian - Native German - Intermediate

EXPERIENCE

MATHEMATICS SCIENCE TUTOR

Self Employed

Remote | Jan 2020 - Present St. Petersburg, Russia | Feb 2009 - Jan 2020

- Teaching mathematics, physics, and computer science to over 70 people ranging from 1st-grade pupils to master degree students from Russia, Israel, Germany, and the UK
- Created and produced a <u>YouTube channel</u> about school mathematics (in Russian) that has over 120 videos, over 40k subscribers, and over 3M views.

ONLINE COURSE PRODUCER AND CONSULTANT

Self Employed

Remote | Jan 2020 - Present

St. Petersburg, Russia | Apr 2019 - Jan 2020

- Authored 4 B2B online courses on business presentation and public speaking.
- Produced over 15 B2B online courses. Including curriculum consultation, video production and editing, and working with SMEs.
- Conducted 5 multi-day in-person seminars on business presentation and public speaking.
- Worked with both commercial and non-profit organizations.

RESEARCH ENGINEER

ITMO University

St. Petersburg, Russia | Mar 2011 - Jun 2017

- · Mathematical modeling in physical electrochemistry.
- Oversaw grant administration for multiple projects, particularly in the field of quantum technologies.
- Taught a Bachelor's level course in Numerical methods in programming.
- Over <u>13 publications</u> in international journals.
- Over 20 conference presentations.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

DeepLearning.Al June 2023 - <u>coursera.org</u> Grade: 97.5 % <u>Certificate link</u> Winner of YouTube NextUp 2021 YouTube, Google Mar 2021 - <u>Channel link</u> Announcement link Specialist Certificate in General Music Studies Berklee Online Dec 2014 - <u>online.berklee.edu</u> Voice Technique, Music Foundations, Jazz Singing